VPN IP check: 51.195.149.220 UNITED KINGDOM

English اللغه العربيه Русский 中國的 فارسی Türk اردو

bVPN

Login

Sign in

**Privacy Policy**

Hello
=====

Your privacy is important to us and we believe it’s also important that everyone enjoys secure and private access to the internet. Our goal is to provide this access without compromising the privacy of our customers. In this document, we will explain the privacy rules applicable to all information collected or submitted when you access, install, or use our Service, as defined in Terms of Service.

When you use our Service, all data you send is encrypted and we do not inspect, log, see or store what you browse, view, or do online during your encrypted VPN session unless you choose to contact us over a VPN connection and you chose to identify yourself to us via chat or email support.

What information do we collect
==============================

1. The Information you provide for:

* Creating your account such as your name, username, email address, and password
* Purchasing a subscription such as your billing name, address, and payment details. 
* Contacting us e.g. support, inquiries, participate in surveys, provide feedback, or submit information through our service.

2. Information collected when you visit our websites using cookies and other technologies, which are necessary for our website to work smoothly and help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches.
    
3. Technical information such as application diagnostics, non-identifying device information, anonymized analytical information, bandwidth usage, timestamps, and approximate location (we don't use your device’s GPS) which is necessary to suggest the nearest fastest server for you.

How we use your information
===========================

* Your personal information helps us keep you updated with announcements, updates, offers, and promotions, if you don’t want to be on our mailing list, please contact our support team or email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.bvpn.co/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
    
* Also, your personal information helps us to provide, maintain, troubleshoot, improve and support the Service
    
* We also use your personal information for billing and payment purposes.
    
* We may use your information for marketing and advertising purposes in order to understand the effectiveness of our advertising.

Third Parties 
==============

Our websites and Apps may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. We may also use third parties to help us provide you with our Service. Third Parties help us with the following aspects:

* Support platform & email service 
    
* Payment processing
    
* Application analytics and diagnostics
    
* Ads & Marketing purposes

Retention of your personal information
======================================

We only retain your personal information for the period necessary to provide our Service to you, or for as long as you have an account with us in order to fulfill our obligations outlined in this Privacy Policy and our Service. We may also retain personal information if required by law.

Children & Minors
=================

Our Service is not offered to, or intended for, and may not be used by minors as defined by applicable laws in relevant jurisdictions.

Your Privacy Rights
===================

We aim to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your personal information, whenever possible and practical. If you are unable to do so, or you wish to be removed from our systems, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.bvpn.co/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Protection of Personal Information
==================================

The security of your personal information is a very serious matter to us. We take all reasonable, practical and necessary steps to secure your personal information against unauthorized access, loss, or modification. 

International Transfers
=======================

We may transfer the information you provide to us, to a country other than the one you reside in, only for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. 

However, appropriate safeguards shall be provided to ensure that your information will remain safe and receives an adequate level of protection. 

Changes
=======

We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, with or without prior notice to you, consistent with applicable privacy laws and principles. Your continued use of our websites or the Service constitutes your acceptance of our Privacy Policy.

**To provide a better user experience, we use cookies. By clicking or navigating the site, you agree to allow our collection of information.**

X

© 2014 bVPN: The Best VPN - Virtual private network Service Provider with Smoke Tunnel.

[VPN for Business](https://www.bvpn.co/en/vpnforbusiness/) - [VPN for Windows](https://www.bvpn.co/en/vpnforwindows/) - [USA VPN](https://www.bvpn.co/en/usavpn/) - [UK VPN](https://www.bvpn.co/en/ukvpn/) - [VPN for iPhone and iPad](https://www.bvpn.co/en/vpnforios/) - [Privacy Policy](https://www.bvpn.co/en/privacypolicy/) - [VPN for Mac](https://www.bvpn.co/en/vpnformac/) - [Affiliates and Resellers](https://www.bvpn.co/en/affiliatesandresellers/) - [Uninstalling b.VPN](https://www.bvpn.co/en/uninstall/) \- [b.VPN Support](https://www.bvpn.co/en/support/) - [b.VPN Discount](https://www.bvpn.co/en/discount/) - [Terms of service](https://www.bvpn.co/en/termsofservice/) - [Stream with bVPN: Your Ticket to Seamless UK Content Streaming Anywhere](https://www.bvpn.co/en/stream_UK_TV/) \- [VPN for Android](https://www.bvpn.co/en/vpnforandroid/) - [VPN service for Iran - Tehran - Mashhad- MTN Irancell - Hamrahe Aval MCI - 4G or 5G network.](https://www.bvpn.co/en/vpn_works_in_Iran/) - [VPN service for Russia - Moscow - Saint Petersburg - MTS - Beeline - MegaFon - 4G or 5G network.](https://www.bvpn.co/en/vpn_works_in_Russia/)
